A Finding Aid to the Leo Castelli Gallery Records, circa 1880-2000, bulk 1957-1999, in the Archives of American Art AAA.leocast
Archives of American Art
- Artists Files, 1913-1999, bulk 1960s-1990s; Series 4; (Boxes 57-133, 197-208, OVs 242-243; 89.5 linear feet)
  - Artists Files, 1938-1999; 4.1
    - Flavin, Dan, 1979; (Oversized material housed in Box 198, Folder 8) (Box 64, Folder 16)
    - Flavin, Dan, 1980-1981 (Box 64, Folder 17)
    - Flavin, Dan, 1982-1983 (Box 64, Folder 18)
    - Flavin, Dan, 1984-1985; (Oversized material housed in Box 198, Folder 8) (Box 64, Folder 19)
    - Flavin, Dan, 1986-1987; (Oversized material housed in Box 198, Folder 8) (Box 64, Folder 20)
    - Flavin, Dan, 1988-1989; (Oversized material housed in Box 198, Folder 8) (Box 64, Folder 21)
    - Flavin, Dan, 1990-1991; (Oversized material housed in Box 198, Folder 8) (Box 64, Folder 22)
    - Flavin, Dan, 1992-1997 (Box 64, Folder 23)
    - French Invasion, 1982; (Oversized material housed in Box 198, Folder 9) (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Furniture Designed by Artists, 1972-1973 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Gaines, Charles, 1978, 1980-1981, 1985, 1987-1988, 1991, 1996 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Gallagher, Carole, 1978, 1980-1981 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Garouste, Gerard, 1979-1982 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Garouste, Gerard, 1982-1983; (Oversized material housed in Box 198, Folder 10) (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Garouste, Gerard, 1984-1986; (Oversized material housed in Box 198, Folder 10) (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Garouste, Gerard, 1986-1987 (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - Garouste, Gerard, 1988; 2 Folders (Box 65, Folder 9-10)
    - Garouste, Gerard, 1988, 1990-1994, 1996; (Oversized material housed in Box 198, Folder 10) (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - Gehry, Frank, 1988 (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - Gibson, Ralph, 1970-1983; (Oversized material housed in Box 198, Folder 11) (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - Gibson, Ralph, 1985-1986 (Box 65, Folder 14)
    - Gibson, Ralph, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 15)
    - Gibson, Ralph, 1988 (Box 65, Folder 16)
    - Gibson, Ralph, 1989-1990 (Box 65, Folder 17)
    - Gibson, Ralph, 1991 (Box 65, Folder 18)
    - Gibson, Ralph, 1991 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Gibson, Ralph, 1992-1996; (Oversized material housed in Box 198, Folder 11) (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Gillette, Frank, circa 1976 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Glass, Philip, 1971-1976, 1984, 1991 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Gorgoni, Gianfranco, circa 1978, 1985-1986 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Graves, Nancy, 1972-1973 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Greenfield-Sanders, Timothy, 1987 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Grisi, Laura, 1966-1971, 1975 (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - Grisi, Laura, 1976-1978 (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - Grisi, Laura, 1979-1981 (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - Grisi, Laura, 1982-1996 (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - Higgins, Ed, 1960-1962 (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - Higgins, Ed, 1962 (Box 66, Folder 13)
    - Higgins, Ed, 1963-1964 (Box 66, Folder 14)
    - Higgins, Ed, 1965-1967 (Box 66, Folder 15)
    - Higgins, Ed, 1968 (Box 66, Folder 16)
    - Horn, Roni, 1983 (Box 66, Folder 17)
    - Horn, Roni, 1984-1987 (Box 66, Folder 18)
    - Horn, Roni, 1988 (Box 66, Folder 19)
    - Horn, Roni, 1989-1992; (Oversized material housed in Box 199, Folder 1) (Box 66, Folder 20)
    - Hsu, Ti Shan, 1986-1987; (Oversized material housed in Box 199, Folder 2) (Box 66, Folder 21)
    - Hsu, Ti Shan, 1987-1989, 1991 (Box 66, Folder 22)
    - Huebler, Douglas, 1968-1971 (Box 66, Folder 23)
    - Huebler, Douglas, 1972; (Oversized material housed in Box 199, Folder 3) (Box 66, Folder 24)
    - Huebler, Douglas, 1973 (Box 66, Folder 25)
    - Huebler, Douglas, 1974; (Oversized material housed in Box 199, Folder 3) (Box 66, Folder 26)
    - Huebler, Douglas, 1975 (Box 66, Folder 27)
    - Huebler, Douglas, 1976-1977 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Huebler, Douglas, 1978 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Huebler, Douglas, 1979-1981; (Oversized material housed in Box 199, Folder 3) (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Huebler, Douglas, 1982-1984; (Oversized material housed in Box 199, Folder 3) (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Huebler, Douglas, 1985-1988; (Oversized material housed in Box 199, Folder 3) (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Huebler, Douglas, 1989-1991; (Oversized material housed in Box 199, Folder 3) (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Johns, Jasper, 1958-1959 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Johns, Jasper, 1960-1961 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - Johns, Jasper, 1962 (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - Johns, Jasper, 1963; (Oversized material housed in Box 199, Folder 4) (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Johns, Jasper, 1964; (Oversized material housed in Box 199, Folder 4) (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - Johns, Jasper, 1965 (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - Johns, Jasper, 1966 (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - Johns, Jasper, 1966-1967 (Box 67, Folder 14)
    - Johns, Jasper, 1968 (Box 67, Folder 15)
    - Johns, Jasper, circa 1968 (Box 67, Folder 16)
    - Johns, Jasper, 1969 (Box 67, Folder 17)
    - Johns, Jasper, 1970 (Box 67, Folder 18)
    - Johns, Jasper, 1971; (2 folders; Oversized material housed in Box 199, Folder 4) (Box 67, Folder 19-20)
    - Johns, Jasper, 1972-1973; (Oversized material housed in Box 199, Folder 4) (Box 67, Folder 21)
    - Johns, Jasper, 1974-1975 (Box 67, Folder 22)
    - Johns, Jasper, 1975 (Box 67, Folder 23)
    - Johns, Jasper, 1976; (Oversized material housed in Box 199, Folder 4) (Box 67, Folder 24)
    - Johns, Jasper, 1977; (Oversized material housed in Box 199, Folder 4) (Box 67, Folder 25)
    - Johns, Jasper, 1977; 2 Folders (Box 68, Folder 1-2)
    - Johns, Jasper, 1978; (3 folders; Oversized material housed in Box 199, Folder 4) (Box 68, Folder 3-5)
    - Johns, Jasper - Clippings, 1978 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Johns, Jasper, 1979 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Johns, Jasper, 1980 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Johns, Jasper - Clippings, 1980 (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Johns, Jasper, 1981; (Oversized material housed in Box 199, Folder 5) (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - Johns, Jasper, 1982 (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - Johns, Jasper, 1983 (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - Johns, Jasper, 1984; (Oversized material housed in Box 199, Folder 5) (Box 68, Folder 13)
    - Johns, Jasper, 1985; (Oversized material housed in Box 199, Folder 5) (Box 68, Folder 14)
    - Johns, Jasper, 1986; 3 Folders (Box 68, Folder 15-17)
    - Johns, Jasper, 1987; (4 folders; Oversized material housed in Box 199, Folder 5) (Box 68, Folder 18-21)
    - Johns, Jasper - Clippings, 1987 (Box 68, Folder 22)
    - Johns, Jasper, circa 1987-1988 (Box 68, Folder 23)
    - Johns, Jasper, 1988; (Oversized material housed in Box 199, Folder 5) (Box 68, Folder 24)
    - Johns, Jasper, 1988 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Johns, Jasper - Clippings, 1988 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Johns, Jasper, 1989; 4 Folders (Box 69, Folder 3-6)
    - Johns, Jasper - Book, 1989 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Johns, Jasper, 1990; (3 folders; Oversized material housed in Box 199, Folder 5) (Box 69, Folder 8-10)
    - Johns, Jasper - Clippings, 1990 (Box 69, Folder 11)
    - Johns, Jasper, 1991; (3 folders; Oversized material housed in Box 199, Folder 5) (Box 69, Folder 12-14)
    - Johns, Jasper, 1992; 4 Folders (Box 69, Folder 15-18)
    - Johns, Jasper, 1993; 3 Folders (Box 69, Folder 19-21)
    - Johns, Jasper, circa 1993 (Box 69, Folder 22)
    - Johns, Jasper, 1994; (Oversized material housed in Box 199, Folder 6) (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - Johns, Jasper, 1995 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Johns, Jasper, circa 1995 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Johns, Jasper, 1996; (5 folders; Oversized material housed in Box 199, Folder 6) (Box 70, Folder 4-8)
    - Johns, Jasper - MOMA Media Coverage, 1997 (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - Johns, Jasper, circa 1997 (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - Johns, Jasper, 1998-1999; (Oversized material housed in Box 199, Folder 6) (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - Johnson, Cletus, 1974-1982; (Oversized material housed in Box 199, Folder 7) (Box 70, Folder 12)
    - Johnson, Cletus, 1983-1992 (Box 70, Folder 13)
    - Johnson, Poppy, 1976, 1978, 1980; (Oversized material housed in Box 199, Folder 8) (Box 70, Folder 14)
    - Judd, Donald, 1964-1966; (Oversized material housed in Box 199, Folder 9) (Box 70, Folder 15)
    - Judd, Donald, 1967 (Box 70, Folder 16)
    - Judd, Donald, 1968 (Box 70, Folder 17)
    - Judd, Donald, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 18)
    - Judd, Donald, 1970-1971; (Oversized material housed in Box 199, Folder 9) (Box 70, Folder 19)
    - Judd, Donald, 1972; (Oversized material housed in Box 199, Folder 9) (Box 70, Folder 20)
    - Judd, Donald, 1973; (Oversized material housed in Box 199, Folder 9) (Box 70, Folder 21)
    - Judd, Donald, 1974-1975 (Box 70, Folder 22)
    - Judd, Donald, 1976; (Oversized material housed in Box 199, Folder 9) (Box 70, Folder 23)
    - Judd, Donald, 1977; (Oversized material housed in Box 199, Folder 9) (Box 70, Folder 24)
    - Judd, Donald, 1978-1979; (Oversized material housed in Box 199, Folder 9) (Box 70, Folder 25)
    - Judd, Donald, 1980; (Oversized material housed in Box 199, Folder 9) (Box 70, Folder 26)
    - Judd, Donald, 1981; (Oversized material housed in Box 199, Folder 9) (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Judd, Donald, 1982; (Oversized material housed in Box 199, Folder 9) (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Judd, Donald, 1983; (Oversized material housed in Box 199, Folder 9) (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Judd, Donald, 1984 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Judd, Donald, 1985 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - Judd, Donald, 1987 (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - Judd, Donald, 1988-1990 (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - Judd, Donald, 1994-1997 (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - Kelly, Ellsworth, 1961-1972; (Oversized material housed in Box 199, Folder 10) (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - Kelly, Ellsworth, 1973 (Box 71, Folder 10)
    - Kelly, Ellsworth, 1973-1974 (Box 71, Folder 11)
    - Kelly, Ellsworth, 1975-1976; (Oversized material housed in Box 199, Folder 10) (Box 71, Folder 12)
    - Kelly, Ellsworth, 1977-1978; (Oversized material housed in Box 199, Folder 10) (Box 71, Folder 13)
    - Kelly, Ellsworth, 1979; (2 folders; Oversized material housed in Box 199, Folder 10) (Box 71, Folder 14-15)
    - Kelly, Ellsworth, 1980; (2 folders; Oversized material housed in Box 199, Folder 10) (Box 71, Folder 16-17)
    - Kelly, Ellsworth, 1981; (Oversized material housed in Box 199, Folder 10) (Box 71, Folder 18)
    - Kelly, Ellsworth, 1982-1983; (Oversized material housed in Box 199, Folder 10) (Box 71, Folder 19)
    - Kelly, Ellsworth, 1984-1985 (Box 71, Folder 20)
    - Kelly, Ellsworth, 1986 (Box 71, Folder 21)
    - Kelly, Ellsworth, 1987-1988 (Box 71, Folder 22)
    - Kelly, Ellsworth, 1989; (Oversized material housed in Box 199, Folder 10) (Box 71, Folder 23)
    - Kelly, Ellsworth, 1990-1991 (Box 71, Folder 24)
    - Kelly, Ellsworth, 1992; (2 folders; Oversized material housed in Box 199, Folder 10) (Box 71, Folder 25-26)
    - Kelly, Ellsworth, 1993 (Box 71, Folder 27)
    - Kelly, Ellsworth, 1994 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Kelly, Ellsworth, 1995-1996 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Kelly, Ellsworth, 1996; (Oversized material housed in Box 199, Folder 10) (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Kelly, Ellsworth, 1996-1997 (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Klein, Yves, circa 1960-1962 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Koons, Jeff, 1988-1996 (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Kosuth, Joseph, 1963-1970; (Oversized material housed in Box 199, Folder 11) (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Kosuth, Joseph, 1971-1972 (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - Kosuth, Joseph, 1973-1974; (Oversized material housed in Box 199, Folder 11) (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - Kosuth, Joseph, 1975-1976; (Oversized material housed in Box 199, Folder 11) (Box 72, Folder 10)
    - Kosuth, Joseph, 1977-1978 (Box 72, Folder 11)
    - Kosuth, Joseph, 1979 (Box 72, Folder 12)
    - Kosuth, Joseph, 1980-1981; (Oversized material housed in Box 199, Folder 11) (Box 72, Folder 13)
    - Kosuth, Joseph, 1982-1983; (Oversized material housed in Box 199, Folder 11) (Box 72, Folder 14)
    - Kosuth, Joseph, 1984-1987; (Oversized material housed in Box 199, Folder 11) (Box 72, Folder 15)
    - Kosuth, Joseph, 1987 (Box 72, Folder 16)
    - Kosuth, Joseph, 1988 (Box 72, Folder 17)
    - Kosuth, Joseph, 1988-1989; (Oversized material housed in Box 199, Folder 11) (Box 72, Folder 18)
    - Kosuth, Joseph, 1990-1991; (Oversized material housed in Box 199, Folder 11) (Box 72, Folder 19)
    - Kosuth, Joseph, 1991 (Box 72, Folder 20)
    - Kosuth, Joseph, 1992; (Oversized material housed in Box 213, Folder 11) (Box 72, Folder 21)
    - Kosuth, Joseph, 1993-1994 (Box 72, Folder 22)
    - Kosuth, Joseph, 1995-1998 (Box 72, Folder 23)
    - Kricke, Norbert, 1961 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Krueger, Jack, circa 1968 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Landry, Richard, 1976-1977 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Landsman, Stanley, 1967-1970 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Langlais, Bernard, circa 1961-1962 (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Lavier, Bertrand, 1986 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Lavier, Bertrand, 1986-1991 (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - Lavier, Bertrand, 1991 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - Lavier, Bertrand, 1991-1994 (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - Lichtenstein, Roy, 1951-1954, 1957, 1962-1963 (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - Lichtenstein, Roy, 1963; (Oversized material housed in Box 200, Folder 1) (Box 73, Folder 11)
    - Lichtenstein, Roy, 1964; (Oversized material housed in Box 200, Folder 1) (Box 73, Folder 12)
    - Lichtenstein, Roy, 1965 (Box 73, Folder 13)
    - Lichtenstein, Roy, 1966; (Oversized material housed in Box 200, Folder 1) (Box 73, Folder 14)
    - Lichtenstein, Roy, 1966-1967 (Box 73, Folder 15)
    - Lichtenstein, Roy, 1967 (Box 73, Folder 16)
    - Lichtenstein, Roy, 1968 (Box 73, Folder 17)
    - Lichtenstein, Roy, 1968-1969 (Box 73, Folder 18)
    - Lichtenstein, Roy, 1970 (Box 73, Folder 19)
    - Lichtenstein, Roy, 1970-1971; (Oversized material housed in Box 200, Folder 1) (Box 73, Folder 20)
    - Lichtenstein, Roy, 1972-1973; (Oversized material housed in Box 200, Folder 1) (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Lichtenstein, Roy, 1974; (Oversized material housed in Box 200, Folder 1) (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Lichtenstein, Roy, 1975; (Oversized material housed in Box 200, Folder 2) (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - Lichtenstein, Roy, 1976; (Oversized material housed in Box 200, Folder 2) (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Lichtenstein, Roy, 1977; 2 Folders (Box 74, Folder 5-6)
    - Lichtenstein, Roy, 1977-1978; (Oversized material housed in Box 200, Folder 2) (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Lichtenstein, Roy, 1978-1979 (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - Lichtenstein, Roy, 1979; 2 Folders (Box 74, Folder 9-10)
    - Lichtenstein, Roy, 1980; (Oversized material housed in Box 200, Folder 2) (Box 74, Folder 11)
    - Lichtenstein, Roy, 1981; (2 folders; Oversized material housed in Box 200, Folder 2) (Box 74, Folder 12-13)
    - Lichtenstein, Roy, 1982 (Box 74, Folder 14)
    - Lichtenstein, Roy, 1983; (2 folders; Oversized material housed in Box 200, Folder 2) (Box 74, Folder 15-16)
    - Lichtenstein, Roy, 1984; 2 Folders (Box 74, Folder 17-18)
    - Lichtenstein, Roy, 1985 (Box 74, Folder 19)
    - Lichtenstein, Roy, 1986 (Box 74, Folder 20)
    - Lichtenstein, Roy, 1986-1987 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Lichtenstein, Roy, 1987; (Oversized material housed in Box 200, Folder 2) (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Lichtenstein, Roy, 1988; (3 folders; Oversized material housed in Box 200, Folder 2) (Box 75, Folder 3-5)
    - Lichtenstein, Roy, 1989; (2 folders; Oversized material housed in Box 200, Folder 2) (Box 75, Folder 6-7)
    - Lichtenstein, Roy, 1990 (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - Lichtenstein, Roy, 1991; (4 folders; Oversized material housed in Box 200, Folder 2) (Box 75, Folder 9-12)
    - Lichtenstein, Roy, 1992; (3 folders; Oversized material housed in Box 200, Folder 2) (Box 75, Folder 13-15)
    - Lichtenstein, Roy, 1993; (3 folders; Oversized material housed in Box 200, Folder 2) (Box 75, Folder 16-18)
    - Lichtenstein, Roy, 1993; 4 Folders (Box 76, Folder 1-4)
    - Lichtenstein, Roy, 1994; 5 Folders (Box 76, Folder 5-9)
    - Lichtenstein, Roy, 1995; (4 folders; Oversized material housed in Box 200, Folder 3) (Box 76, Folder 10-13)
    - Lichtenstein, Roy, 1996; (Oversized material housed in Box 200, Folder 3) (Box 76, Folder 14)
    - Lichtenstein, Roy, 1996-1997 (Box 76, Folder 15)
    - Lichtenstein, Roy - "Roy Lichtenstein y el Arte Pop", 1970 (Box 76, Folder 16)
    - Longo, Robert, 1981-1984 (Box 76, Folder 17)
    - Lord, Andrew, 1992-1993 (Box 76, Folder 18)
    - Lord, Andrew, 1994-1996 (Box 76, Folder 19)
    - Lynch, David, 1987-1990 (Box 76, Folder 20)
    - Mapplethorpe, Robert, 1981-1984 (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Meier, Richard, 1993-1995; (Oversized material housed in Box 200, Folder 4) (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - Merz, Mario, 1985 (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - Mondrian, Piet, 1974 (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Moore, Peter, circa 1960s-1900s; (Oversized material housed in Box 200, Folder 5) (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - Morris, Robert, 1960, 1963-1967; (Oversized material housed in Box 200, Folder 6) (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - Morris, Robert, 1968; (Oversized material housed in Box 200, Folder 6) (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Morris, Robert, 1969 (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - Morris, Robert, 1970; (Oversized material housed in Box 200, Folder 6) (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - Morris, Robert, 1971; (Oversized material housed in Box 200, Folder 6) (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - Morris, Robert, 1972; (Oversized material housed in Box 200, Folder 6) (Box 77, Folder 11)
    - Morris, Robert, 1973; (Oversized material housed in Box 200, Folder 6) (Box 77, Folder 12)
    - Morris, Robert, 1974; (2 folders; Oversized material housed in Box 200, Folder 6) (Box 77, Folder 13-14)
    - Morris, Robert, 1975-1976; (Oversized material housed in Box 200, Folder 6) (Box 77, Folder 15)
    - Morris, Robert, 1977; (Oversized material housed in Box 200, Folder 6) (Box 77, Folder 16)
    - Morris, Robert, 1978; (2 folders; Oversized material housed in Box 200, Folder 6) (Box 77, Folder 17-18)
    - Morris, Robert, 1979; (Oversized material housed in Box 200, Folder 6) (Box 77, Folder 19)
    - Morris, Robert, 1980; (2 folders; Oversized material housed in Box 200, Folder 6) (Box 77, Folder 20-21)
    - Morris, Robert, 1981 (Box 77, Folder 22)
    - Morris, Robert, 1982; (Oversized material housed in Box 200, Folder 6) (Box 77, Folder 23)
    - Morris, Robert, 1983; (Oversized material housed in Box 200, Folder 6) (Box 77, Folder 24)
    - Morris, Robert, 1984 (Box 77, Folder 25)
    - Morris, Robert, 1985; (Oversized material housed in Box 200, Folder 6) (Box 77, Folder 26)
    - Morris, Robert, 1986 (Box 77, Folder 27)
    - Morris, Robert, 1987 (Box 77, Folder 28)
    - Morris, Robert, 1988; (Oversized material housed in Box 200, Folder 6) (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Morris, Robert, 1989 (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - Morris, Robert, 1990; (Oversized material housed in Box 200, Folder 6) (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - Morris, Robert, 1991; (Oversized material housed in Box 200, Folder 6) (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - Morris, Robert, 1992; 2 Folders (Box 78, Folder 5-6)
    - Morris, Robert, 1993 (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - Morris, Robert, 1994; (2 folders; Oversized material housed in Box 200, Folder 6) (Box 78, Folder 8-9)
    - Morris, Robert, circa 1995 (Box 78, Folder 10)
    - Morris, Robert, 1995-1998 (Box 78, Folder 11)
    - Namuth, Hans, 1976, 1982, 1988-1992; (Oversized material housed in Box 200, Folder 7) (Box 78, Folder 12)
    - Nauman, Bruce, 1966-1970; (Oversized material housed in Box 200, Folder 8) (Box 78, Folder 13)
    - Nauman, Bruce, 1971; (Oversized material housed in Box 200, Folder 8) (Box 78, Folder 14)
    - Nauman, Bruce, 1972-1974; (Oversized material housed in Box 200, Folder 8) (Box 78, Folder 15)
    - Nauman, Bruce, 1975; (Oversized material housed in Box 200, Folder 8) (Box 78, Folder 16)
    - Nauman, Bruce, 1976-1979; (Oversized material housed in Box 200, Folder 8) (Box 78, Folder 17)
    - Nauman, Bruce, 1980; 2 Folders (Box 78, Folder 18-19)
    - Nauman, Bruce, 1981; (Oversized material housed in Box 200, Folder 8) (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Nauman, Bruce, 1982-1983; (Oversized material housed in Box 200, Folders 8-9) (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - Nauman, Bruce, 1984-1985 (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - Nauman, Bruce, 1986; (2 folders; Oversized material housed in Box 200, Folder 9) (Box 79, Folder 4-5)
    - Nauman, Bruce, 1987 (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - Nauman, Bruce, 1988; (Oversized material housed in Box 200, Folder 9) (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - Nauman, Bruce, 1989; (Oversized material housed in Box 200, Folder 9) (Box 79, Folder 8)
    - Nauman, Bruce, 1990; (2 folders; Oversized material housed in Box 2000, Folder 9) (Box 79, Folder 9-10)
    - Nauman, Bruce, 1991; 2 Folders (Box 79, Folder 11-12)
    - Nauman, Bruce, 1992; (2 folders; Oversized material housed in Box 200, Folder 9) (Box 79, Folder 13-14)
    - Nauman, Bruce, 1993; (Oversized material housed in Box 201, Folder 1) (Box 79, Folder 15)
    - Nauman, Bruce, 1994; (6 folders; Oversized material housed in Box 201, Folder 1) (Box 79, Folder 16-21)
    - Nauman, Bruce, 1995; (4 folders; Oversized material housed in Box 201, Folder 1) (Box 80, Folder 1-4)
    - Nauman, Bruce, 1996; (Oversized material housed in Box 201, Folder 1) (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - Nauman, Bruce, 1997-1998 (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - Noland, Kenneth, 1961-1976; (Oversized material housed in Box 201, Folder 2) (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - Noland, Kenneth, 1977; (Oversized material housed in Box 201, Folder 2) (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - Noland, Kenneth, 1978; (Oversized material housed in Box 201, Folder 2) (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - Noland, Kenneth, 1979-1981, 1995 (Box 80, Folder 10)
    - Oldenburg, Claes, 1962-1966; (Oversized material housed in Box 201, Folder 3) (Box 80, Folder 11)
    - Oldenburg, Claes, 1967-1969; (Oversized material housed in Box 201, Folder 3) (Box 80, Folder 12)
    - Oldenburg, Claes, 1970-1971 (Box 80, Folder 13)
    - Oldenburg, Claes, 1972-1973; (Oversized material housed in Box 201, Folder 3) (Box 80, Folder 14)
    - Oldenburg, Claes, 1974; (Oversized material housed in Box 201, Folder 3) (Box 80, Folder 15)
    - Oldenburg, Claes, 1975; (2 folders; Oversized material housed in Box 201, Folder 3) (Box 80, Folder 16-17)
    - Oldenburg, Claes, 1976; (3 folders; Oversized material housed in Box 201, Folder 3) (Box 80, Folder 18-20)
    - Oldenburg, Claes, 1977; (Oversized material housed in Box 201, Folder 3) (Box 80, Folder 21)
    - Oldenburg, Claes, 1978 (Box 80, Folder 22)
    - Oldenburg, Claes, 1979 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - Oldenburg, Claes, 1980 (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - Oldenburg, Claes, 1981-1982; (Oversized material housed in Box 201, Folder 3) (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - Oldenburg, Claes, 1983-1984 (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - Oldenburg, Claes, 1985-1986 (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - Oldenburg, Claes, 1986 (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - Oldenburg, Claes, 1987 (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - Oldenburg, Claes, 1988; (Oversized material housed in Box 201, Folder 3) (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - Oldenburg, Claes, 1989 (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - Oldenburg, Claes, 1990 (Box 81, Folder 10)
    - Oldenburg, Claes, 1991; (Oversized material housed in Box 201, Folder 3) (Box 81, Folder 11)
    - Oldenburg, Claes, 1992, 1994-1997 (Box 81, Folder 12)
    - Oldenburg, Claes - Coosje Van Bruggen, circa 1977, 1982, 1990-1991, 1994-1995 (Box 81, Folder 13)
    - Oldenburg, Claes - "Large-Scale Projects, 1977-1980" (Box 81, Folder 14)
    - Owen, Frank, 1971-1975 (Box 81, Folder 15)
    - Pettibone, Richard, 1970 (Box 81, Folder 16)
    - Pollock, Jackson, 1957 (Box 81, Folder 17)
    - Poons, Larry, 1963-1965 (Box 81, Folder 18)
    - Poons, Larry, 1967-1968 (Box 81, Folder 19)
    - Pozzi, Lucio, 1984 (Box 81, Folder 20)
    - Price, Kenneth, 1981-1984; (Oversized material housed in Box 201, Folder 4) (Box 81, Folder 21)
    - Rauschenberg, Robert, 1951, 1958-1959 (Box 81, Folder 22)
    - Rauschenberg, Robert, circa 1960s; 2 Folders (Box 82, Folder 1-2)
    - Rauschenberg, Robert, 1960-1961 (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - Rauschenberg, Robert, 1961 (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - Rauschenberg, Robert, 1961-1962 (Box 82, Folder 5)